<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configure ignore rules on</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ignore-rules/</link><description>Recent content in Configure ignore rules on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ignore-rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuring global ignore rules</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ignore-rules/global/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ignore-rules/global/</guid><description>Ignore rules can be set up globally for a BluBracket tenant. blubracket-ignore.yaml allows Blubracket users to ignore specific secret types, secret values, or paths. This file must be sent utilizing the Blubracket API’s. When a match of the ignore file is made, an alert will not be created however an event will still be made.
Note: This will not change any existing alerts/events in the platform.
Download integration API key</description></item><item><title>Configuring ignore rules per repo</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ignore-rules/per-repo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ignore-rules/per-repo/</guid><description>In some cases a repo administrator may want to ignore specific secret types, secret values, or paths for all commits by any contributor to that repo. This can be achieved by creating an ignore.yaml file. This file is then placed into the root directory of the repository, within a .blubracket directory at the repo root.
When a match of the ignore file is made, an alert will not be created (but an event will still be generated).</description></item><item><title>Configuring local ignore rules</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ignore-rules/local/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ignore-rules/local/</guid><description>In some cases a developer may want the BluBracket CLI Tool to ignore specific secret types or entire files. This can be achieved by creating a .blubracket-ignore file. This file is then placed into the root directory of the repository.
The format of the .blubracket-ignore file is similar to a .gitignore file.
Empty lines and lines beginning with # will be ignored
To ignore all secrets in a file a glob pattern is recognized.</description></item></channel></rss>