<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frequently asked questions on</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/</link><description>Recent content in Frequently asked questions on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What file types are scanned?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/what-file-types-are-scanned/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 01:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/what-file-types-are-scanned/</guid><description>Source code and text files # BluBracket scans for code risks in all text encoded files, regardless of language.
Archives # In addition, we also support scanning binary files. We support the following archive formats with different compression levels.
Zip Rar Tar br bz2 gz lz4 sz xz zstd 7-Zip (Coming soon) In CLI, scanning archive files is supported using scan-dir subcommand.
Note: For Bitbucket Cloud &amp;amp; Server, archive files are only scanned during a full repo scan.</description></item><item><title>Can I customize what secrets are detected by the CLI tool?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/can-i-customize-secrets-detected-by-the-cli/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/can-i-customize-secrets-detected-by-the-cli/</guid><description>Yes. BluBracket can identify hundreds of different types of secrets in code, including tokens, keys, IDs and passwords, but the BluBracket CLI tool also supports user-defined regular expressions to match and alert on.
For more detailed information on how to add regular expressions to the CLI, look here.</description></item><item><title>Can I find secrets before they are committed?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/can-i-find-secrets-before-committed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/can-i-find-secrets-before-committed/</guid><description>Yes. With the BluBracket Command Line Interface (CLI) tool, you can catch secrets before the code is committed to a repository. Once downloaded and configured, the tool will report any risks found in commits and optionally block commits until they&amp;rsquo;re addressed.
The BluBracket CLI tool works with pre-commit hooks, and with any IDEs where the pre-commit hooks are supported.</description></item><item><title>Do I need a credit card to sign up?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/do-i-need-a-credit-card/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/do-i-need-a-credit-card/</guid><description>No credit card is needed to sign up for either the BluBracket Community Edition or the BluBracket Team Edition free trial.
Learn how to sign up here.</description></item><item><title>Do I need a GitHub account to try BluBracket?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/do-i-need-a-github-account-to-start-free/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/do-i-need-a-github-account-to-start-free/</guid><description>A GitHub account is required to create a free account with BluBracket.
Additional users can be added to an account via email.</description></item><item><title>Does BluBracket scan new commits to repositories?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/does-blubracket-scan-new-commits-to-repositories/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/does-blubracket-scan-new-commits-to-repositories/</guid><description>Yes. Each time a new commit is made to a monitored repository, BluBracket immediately scans the commit for any new risks. Any risks that are found will be displayed in the web dashboard, and alerted through any configured alert integrations.</description></item><item><title>Does BluBracket store/modify my code or any part of my code?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/does-blubracket-store-modify-my-code/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/does-blubracket-store-modify-my-code/</guid><description>No. BluBracket clones repositories, scans them, creates a hash of each of the files (for later comparisons), then the entire checkout from the BluBracket servers. All of this happens within a few seconds, depending on the repository size.
After the scan, BluBracket saves specific metadata to support alerting and reporting on any found risks—things like repository names, file names, contributor IDs, commit IDs and times, etc.
BluBracket never stores any code after the scan.</description></item><item><title>How do I add a repo to monitor?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/how-do-i-add-a-repo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/how-do-i-add-a-repo/</guid><description>To monitor a code repository in BluBracket, it must be part of a monitored code server.
👉 How to add code servers
For many code servers supported by BluBracket, you have an option of automatically monitoring all repos on the code server, or choosing which repos to monitor. View your configured code servers in Settings → Code Servers, then select &amp;ldquo;edit monitored repositories&amp;rdquo; from the options menu for the code server:</description></item><item><title>How do I sign in to BluBracket?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/how-to-sign-in-to-blubracket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/how-to-sign-in-to-blubracket/</guid><description>Every BluBracket account uses a different domain name to provide you the most secure, reliable, and personalized experience.
To sign in to your account, go to the account domain in your welcome email and follow the prompts to sign in.
BluBracket provides your login link through email.</description></item><item><title>How does BluBracket IaC scanning compare to Checkov?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/how-does-blubracket-iac-scanning-compare-to-checkov/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/how-does-blubracket-iac-scanning-compare-to-checkov/</guid><description>BluBracket&amp;rsquo;s IaC scanning is built on the open source Checkov scanner, combined with BluBracket&amp;rsquo;s workflow tools optimized to help development teams identify new risks before propagating in code, and knock down the risks already in their code through continuous improvement.
Checkov BluBracket IaC scanning IaC scanning ✅ ✅ Graph-based queries ✅ On roadmap IDE integration ✅ ✅ IaC policy violations ✅ ✅ Custom policies Requires customization On roadmap Notifications ⛔️ ✅ Dashboards ⛔️ ✅ External dependencies/</description></item></channel></rss>