<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frequently asked questions on</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/</link><description>Recent content in Frequently asked questions on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Can I customize what secrets are detected by the CLI tool?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/can-i-customize-secrets-detected-by-the-cli/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/can-i-customize-secrets-detected-by-the-cli/</guid><description>Yes. BluBracket can identify hundreds of different types of secrets in code, including tokens, keys, IDs and passwords, but the BluBracket CLI tool also supports user-defined regular expressions to match and alert on.
For more detailed information on how to add regular expressions to the CLI, look here.</description></item><item><title>Can I find secrets before they are committed?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/can-i-find-secrets-before-committed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/can-i-find-secrets-before-committed/</guid><description>Yes. With the BluBracket Command Line Interface (CLI) tool, you can catch secrets before the code is committed to a repository. Once downloaded and configured, the tool will report any risks found in commits and optionally block commits until they&amp;rsquo;re addressed.
The BluBracket CLI tool works with pre-commit hooks, and with any IDEs where the pre-commit hooks are supported.</description></item><item><title>Does BluBracket scan new commits to repositories?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/does-blubracket-scan-new-commits-to-repositories/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/does-blubracket-scan-new-commits-to-repositories/</guid><description>Yes. Each time a new commit is made to a monitored repository, BluBracket immediately scans the commit for any new risks. Any risks that are found will be displayed in the web dashboard, and alerted through any configured alert integrations.</description></item><item><title>Does BluBracket store/modify my code or any part of my code?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/does-blubracket-store-modify-my-code/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/does-blubracket-store-modify-my-code/</guid><description>No. BluBracket clones repositories, scans them, creates a hash of each of the files (for later comparisons), then the entire checkout from the BluBracket servers. All of this happens within a few seconds, depending on the repository size.
After the scan, BluBracket saves specific metadata to support alerting and reporting on any found risks—things like repository names, file names, contributor IDs, commit IDs and times, etc.
BluBracket never stores any code after the scan.</description></item><item><title>How do I add a repo to monitor?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/how-do-i-add-a-repo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/how-do-i-add-a-repo/</guid><description>To monitor a code repository in BluBracket, it must be part of a monitored code server.
👉 How to add code servers
For many code servers supported by BluBracket, you have an option of automatically monitoring all repos on the code server, or choosing which repos to monitor. View your configured code servers in Settings → Code Servers, then select &amp;ldquo;edit monitored repositories&amp;rdquo; from the options menu for the code server:</description></item><item><title>How long does it take for BB to scan new commits?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/how-long-does-it-take-to-scan-new-commits/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/how-long-does-it-take-to-scan-new-commits/</guid><description>The time it takes for BluBracket to scan new commits depends on the size of the commit. In most cases though the scan is perceived as immediate.</description></item><item><title>What alerts are shown in BluBracket?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/what-alerts-are-shown/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/what-alerts-are-shown/</guid><description>This page is a stub.</description></item><item><title>What can I do with BluBracket APIs?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/what-can-i-do-with-blubracket-apis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/what-can-i-do-with-blubracket-apis/</guid><description>Use BluBracket APIs to integrate with your CI/DC solution. This will help make sure that there are no secrets accidentally checked in to code by any of your team members.
You may also leverage BluBracket APIs to export secret found events to other systems in addition to our support for Slack, Splunk, and others.</description></item><item><title>What does the BluBracket CLI tool do?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/what-does-the-cli-tool-do/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/what-does-the-cli-tool-do/</guid><description>The BluBracket CLI tool provides a number of developer conveniences, and is optimized to check for the following at git pre-commit:
Secrets:the tool identifies hundreds of types of tokens, keys, IDs as well as passwords. Non-inclusive language: the tool identifies non-inclusive language like master, slave, dummy, and blacklist. Custom RegEx: you can configure your own regular expressions that the tool will identify and alert on. Commit Signing:the CLI can check that the commit is going to be signed or not.</description></item><item><title>What GitHub permissions does the BluBracket app require?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/what-permissions-do-you-require/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/faq/what-permissions-do-you-require/</guid><description>When you authenticate into BluBracket using GitHub Oauth you will see and approve the following permissions:
Read access to administration, code, members, metadata, organization administration, and pull requests Read and write access to checks, organization hooks, and repository hooks These permissions allow BluBracket to monitor the repositories that you select and present you with any secrets found as well as contributor/commit information.</description></item></channel></rss>