<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CI checks on</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ci-checks/</link><description>Recent content in CI checks on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ci-checks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure BitBucket Code Insights</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ci-checks/bitbucket-insights/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ci-checks/bitbucket-insights/</guid><description>Prerequisites # This integration depends on an API endpoint to fetch the pull request details from the commit. This API endpoint specifically requires pull request links to be indexed, which means that within the lifetime of the repository a user has to have clicked “go to pull request” from the per commit view of the Bitbucket Cloud UI at least once.
The &amp;lsquo;go to pull request&amp;rsquo; link in the commit view of the Bitbucket Cloud UI</description></item><item><title>Configure GitHub Checks</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ci-checks/github-checks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/ci-checks/github-checks/</guid><description>Prerequisites # To install the BluBracket app for GitHub Checks, permissions to install a GitHub App on an org are required. This would be an organization owner or someone with admin level permissions in a repository.
Choosing which app to install # The BluBracket app for GitHub Checks is available for all BluBracket editions, and multiple offerings of GitHub.
GitHub Cloud GitHub Enterprise
(including Server) BluBracket Community Edition BluBracket Community &amp;amp; Team Edition n/a BluBracket Team Edition BluBracket Community &amp;amp; Team Edition n/a BluBracket Enterprise Edition BluBracket Enterprise Edition BluBracket Enterprise Edition &amp;amp; GitHub Enterprise Server GitHub Checks setup for GitHub Cloud and BluBracket Community &amp;amp; Team Edition accounts # BluBracket Community and Team Edition accounts are monitored by the BluBracket Community Edition app.</description></item></channel></rss>