<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User guide on</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/</link><description>Recent content in User guide on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adding a BluBracket user</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-user/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-user/</guid><description>The first thing you might want to do is add your team members to assist with the setup and management. As soon as you log into your BluBracket tenant, you should create at least one additional user for the admin portal:
Go to Settings.
Click the Users Tab.
Click Add User Assign a unique username.
Enter the user’s email address.</description></item><item><title>Configure Azure AD</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-user-ad-saml/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-user-ad-saml/</guid><description>BluBracket supports single sign-on and federated identity services with Azure Active Directory using SAML. This article covers configuring the BluBracket app in Azure AD, configuring the Azure AD SAML federation in BluBracket, and managing users.
Once single sign-on is configured as described below, authentication, passwords, and two-factor authentication are managed and configured in Azure AD.
However, users must be registered in both BluBracket and Azure AD. Removing a user from either Azure or BluBracket will terminate their access to BluBracket.</description></item><item><title>Remediate alerts</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/remediate-alerts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/remediate-alerts/</guid><description>There are a number of best practices when it comes to handling secrets in code. Below are a few:
Encrypt your secrets
Use environmental variables
Use a secret manager to store your secrets, like HashiCorp Vault, Azure Key Vault, etc.
Once BluBracket has found a secret and you have had a chance to remediate the secret in code, marking it as reviewed will help you easily differentiate it from those that still require action.</description></item><item><title>Integration architecture</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/architecture/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/architecture/</guid><description>BluBracket runs as SaaS, on-prem, or in your VPC, and integrates with a variety of cloud-hosted or on-prem tools to secure your entire code pipeline from developer to deploy.
BluBracket architecture diagram. View larger.
Risk detection orchestration engine # BluBracket executes risk scanners on-demand, in response to events like new code pushes or pull requests, and on a periodic schedule as appropriate for the resource being scanned and user needs.</description></item></channel></rss>