<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SAML Setup on</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/saml-setup/</link><description>Recent content in SAML Setup on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/saml-setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure Okta</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/saml-setup/okta/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/saml-setup/okta/</guid><description>BluBracket supports single sign-on and federated identity services with Okta using SAML. This article covers configuring the BluBracket app in Okta, configuring the Okta SAML federation in BluBracket, and managing users.
Once single sign-on is configured as described below, authentication, passwords, and two-factor authentication are managed and configured in Okta.
However unless role based access is enabled, users must be registered in both BluBracket and Okta. Removing a user from either Okta or BluBracket will terminate their access to BluBracket.</description></item><item><title>Configure Ping Identity</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/saml-setup/ping/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/saml-setup/ping/</guid><description>BluBracket supports single sign-on and federated identity services with Ping using SAML. This article covers configuring the BluBracket app in Ping, configuring the Ping SAML federation in BluBracket, and managing users.
Once single sign-on is configured as described below, authentication, passwords, and two-factor authentication are managed and configured in Ping.
However unless role based access is enabled, users must be registered in both BluBracket and Ping. Removing a user from either Ping or BluBracket will terminate their access to BluBracket.</description></item><item><title>Configure Azure AD</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/saml-setup/azure-ad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/saml-setup/azure-ad/</guid><description>BluBracket supports single sign-on and federated identity services with Azure Active Directory using SAML. This article covers configuring the BluBracket app in Azure AD, configuring the Azure AD SAML federation in BluBracket, and managing users.
Once single sign-on is configured as described below, authentication, passwords, and two-factor authentication are managed and configured in Azure AD.
However, users must be registered in both BluBracket and Azure AD. Removing a user from either Azure or BluBracket will terminate their access to BluBracket.</description></item></channel></rss>