<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Adding code servers on</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-code-servers/</link><description>Recent content in Adding code servers on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-code-servers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adding a GitHub cloud server to your tenant</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-code-servers/github-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-code-servers/github-cloud/</guid><description>The first step in setting up a BluBracket tenant is adding your code servers. This enables the BluBracket servers to communicate with your companies GitHub services, which are necessary to generate alerts/events and reports. In this document, we will walk through the necessary steps to successfully add your GitHub enterprise code server to BluBracket. The following is a breakdown of the steps:
Navigating to the Enterprise Code Servers section of the Settings page</description></item><item><title>Adding A Bitbucket Cloud Server To Your Tenant</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-code-servers/bitbucket-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-code-servers/bitbucket-cloud/</guid><description>The first step in setting up a BluBracket tenant is adding your code servers. This enables the BluBracket servers to communicate with your companies Bitbucket services, which are necessary to generate alerts/events and reports. In this document, we will walk through the necessary steps to successfully add your Bitbucket enterprise code server to BluBracket. The following is a breakdown of the steps:
Navigating to the Enterprise Code Servers section of the Settings page</description></item><item><title>Adding a GitLab cloud server to your tenant</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-code-servers/gitlab-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/how-to/add-code-servers/gitlab-cloud/</guid><description>The first step in setting up a BluBracket tenant is adding your code servers. This enables the BluBracket servers to communicate with your companies GitLab services, which are necessary to generate alerts/events and reports. In this document, we will walk through the necessary steps to successfully add your GitLab enterprise code server to BluBracket. The following is a breakdown of the steps:
Navigating to the Enterprise Code Servers section of the Settings page</description></item></channel></rss>