<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction to BluBracket on</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction to BluBracket on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is BluBracket?</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/what-is-blubracket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/what-is-blubracket/</guid><description>BluBracket is a code and git security suite that identifies risks in your code, monitors who and what has access to your code, and tracks where your code goes outside your git repos.
BluBracket use-cases # Identifying, preventing, and removing risks in code Secrets Personally identifiable information (PII) Non-inclusive language (NIL) Code analysis (SAST) Infrastructure-as-code (IAC) risks Dependency vulnerabilities Monitoring who and what has access to your code Monitoring where your code goes Who is BluBracket for?</description></item><item><title>BluBracket use-cases</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/use-cases/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/use-cases/</guid><description>BluBracket is most often used to identify risks in code, who has access, and where it goes:
Identifying, preventing, and removing risks in code Secrets Personally identifiable information (PII) Non-inclusive language (NIL) Code analysis (SAST) Infrastructure-as-code (IAC) risks Dependency vulnerabilities Monitoring who and what has access to your code Monitoring where your code goes Secrets in code # Passwords, keys, and other secrets in code are no longer secret when code is shared across teams, repos are made public, or when employees leave with copies of the code.</description></item><item><title>Getting started with BluBracket</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/getting-started/</guid><description>Getting started with BluBracket is a three step process:
Sign up Add a code server Start improving security Signing up # To start using BluBracket for free, visit our signup page and click the start for free button.
Begin your three-step process by clicking the start for free button.
Then approve the GitHub OAuth request.
Accept the GitHub OAuth request.
After authenticating and approving the permissions to sign in with GitHub, we&amp;rsquo;ll create a free account for you.</description></item><item><title>Key workflows</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/key-workflows/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/key-workflows/</guid><description>BluBracket code security tools are optimized to prevent risks from getting into code, and to promote the process of continuous improvement that reduces existing risks from code over time.
Preventing risks in code # As developers, we depend on a quick feedback loop to understand if our code is working and does what is expected. BluBracket tools can offer automated security guidance as part of that feedback loop, in the IDE of your choice, pre-commit, and as part of the CI flow.</description></item><item><title>Integrations</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/integrations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/intro/integrations/</guid><description>Local workflow tools # The BluBracket CLI tool can identify and block secrets before they&amp;rsquo;re committed.
Available local tools and integrations
CLI IntelliJ (via CLI, full plugin coming soon) Visual Studio Code (via CLI) Usage guide: installing and using the CLI .
Code servers # BluBracket scans repositories hosted in GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket, and others.
Certified &amp;amp; supported code servers:</description></item></channel></rss>