<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release notes on</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/</link><description>Recent content in Release notes on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2021-11-22 release</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-11-22/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-11-22/</guid><description>New Features and Enhancements # “Other” type has been added to the Secret Types pie chart on the BluPrint page. The pie chart should now show the top 6 secret types as well as a 7th that is composed of all of the remaining types. Clicking on any of the pie sections should take the user to a filtered table for the selected secret type. Many additional enhancements have been added to identify false positives where secrets are concerned.</description></item><item><title>2021-10-11 release</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-10-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-10-11/</guid><description>New Features and Enhancements # New public API to return repo scan status Added infinite label filter to support scrolling through all labels. Bug Fixes # CORE-8192 URL of webhook was not displayed in the compliance alerts flyover details CORE-8343 Enhanced false positive detection where secret type is “token” CORE-8414 - Fixed Slack integration issue where deep link was not being displayed in message Fix table pagination loading bugs</description></item><item><title>2021-09-28 release</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-09-28/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-09-28/</guid><description>New Features and Enhancements # Additional checks performed when user adds new code server. We now identify and show a message if the user does not have adequate organization level permissions, even if the Personal Access Token does have required permissions. Inadequate user permissions will result in incomplete repo risk calculations.
Code Leaks now filters out Public to Public alerts.
Code Leaks details now displays a deep link to the selected leaked file</description></item><item><title>2021-09-13 release</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-09-13/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-09-13/</guid><description>New Features and Enhancements # New Repo Details Design. When clicking on a Repository, you will now see a new design that lists the risk rating and number of violations for each risk category. Clicking on the violations number will provide a filter view of all violations of that risk category type.
The terminology “Alerts” has been replaced with “All Violations”, which is a new tab next to Code Risks at top of screen.</description></item><item><title>2021-09-07 release</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-09-07/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-09-07/</guid><description>New Features and Enhancements # Access Risk Categories now links to appropriate alerts in the repo details page.
Enhanced Code Server onboarding for Bitbucket and GitLab.
Updated Infrastructure Code Alerts and Events to be more descriptive.
Added breadcrumbs to repository details page in portal.
Updated support for global Ignore.yaml. If you place a folder labeled “.blubracket” into a repository, then create a file called ignore.</description></item><item><title>2021-08-16 release</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-08-16/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-08-16/</guid><description>New Features and Enhancements # Enterprise Edition # New Code Risks Categories
BluBracket has added two additional Risk Categories to the repo detail view, PII and Non-inclusive language!
All newly created tenants will automatically have three Non-inclusive language regular expressions configured (blacklist, slave, master) and one PII regular expression for social security numbers.
For existing customers, if you would like to utilize the new PII and Non-inclusive Language categories, please follow the instructions below:</description></item><item><title>2021-07-21 release</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-07-21/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-07-21/</guid><description>New Features and Enhancements # Enterprise Edition # No new features or enhancements added to the Enterprise Edition with this release.
Community Edition # No new features or enhancements added to the Community Edition with this release.
Bug Fixes # CORE-7410 - Fix filtering issue when attempting to filter for a value that does not exist. Now returns “no events found” instead of returning all results.
CORE-7514 - Fix custom date range bug for Last Activity column in repository list view</description></item><item><title>2021-07-03 release</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-07-03/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-07-03/</guid><description>New Features and Enhancements # Enterprise Edition # Code Risks # Within the repository details page the Code Risks tab now indicates the level of risk associated with any of the risk categories that BluBracket could potentially be identifying. As seen in the screenshot below, all categories are designated with a High/Medium/Low indicator and the number of violations associated with the risk category type. Clicking risk category type will navigate the user to a list view of the violations.</description></item><item><title>2021-06-05 release</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-06-05/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-06-05/</guid><description>New Features and Enhancements # Enterprise Edition # High Risks # The BluPrint page now contains a new table that displays the most risky repos that are currently being monitored. The repository with the highest risk score is at the top of the list, descending to the 100th highest at the bottom. The Alert tiles have been moved to just below this table and are now, by default, in a collapsed state.</description></item><item><title>2021-05-03 release</title><link>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-05-03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 02:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.blubracket.com/release-notes/2021-05-03/</guid><description>New Features and Enhancements # Enterprise Edition # Event Tagging and Alert Enabling # Event Tagging: For quite some time now BluBracket has been using tagging events with things like “Active Token”, “Inactive Token”, “Strong Password”, etc. These tags have been used to notify the user of specific information related to the event. It quickly became apparent that these could be useful for customers when integrating with other systems, or just for filtering purposes.</description></item></channel></rss>